WhatsApp: +1-3523898104 [support@hostathash.com](mailto:support@hostathash.com)

* Already have an Account ?

[

](https://hostathash.com/)

* Domain
* Shared Host
* VPS
* Servers

Select Page

**Privacy Policy**
==================

HostatHash (“We”, “Company”, “Our”, or “Us”) is the owner of hostathash.com (“Website”). We respect the online privacy of the visitors of this Website (“You” or “Your”) through our compliance with the provisions contained in this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). This Policy, essentially, informs you about the kind of information we collect, how we use, protect and sometimes disclose such information while you are using the Website service.

Please read this Policy document carefully. If you do not agree with any of the provisions contained herein, you understand and agree that your sole remedy shall be the immediate cessation of Website service in any form and manner whatsoever.

### **Amendments**

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time, in our sole discretion and without any prior information to anyone. All such amendments shall be effective on their posting on this Website page. Your continued use of the Website service signifies your implied acceptance of such amended Policy. You are requested to visit this page periodically in order to remain updated on the amended Policy.

### **Applicability**

This Policy shall be applicable on the information collected through the Website, any email, text or electronic communication with you, or through mobile-based application that enables use of the service, which is otherwise provided online through the Website.

### **Privacy of Children**

The Website service is intended for use by persons who are eligible to enter into a valid contract. Therefore, we do not recommend the use of the Website service for children under the age of 18 years. If you are under the age of 18 years, you are requested to stop any further use of the Website service. If you suspect that we are in possession of any information or data related to children below 18 years, please contact us at **support@hostathash.com** for immediate remedial action.

### **Information Collection**

1) Personally Identifiable Information: During your use of the Website service, we may collect certain personally identifiable information including, without limitation,

* your name,
* age,
* gender,
* postal address,
* email address,
* telephone number,
* company name,
* company/personal website URL
* job title and
* other company/personal details.

This information is collected only when you voluntarily provide us with the requested details during your use of the Website service. For instance, without limitation, information submitted while filling forms on the Website (e.g., registration form, order form), reporting a problem in the Website service, responding to surveys and questionnaires.

2) Non-personally Identifiable Information: We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information from your use of the Website service, which does not directly identify you. This information may include, without limitation,

* the operating system installed on your computer system,
* the browser you used to access the Website,
* your Internet Protocol (IP) Address,
* the IP Address of your Internet Service Provider (ISP),
* location data,
* traffic data,
* communication data,
* browsing patterns (for instance, Website pages most visited, time spent on each page, action taken on each page, etc.)

The non-personally identifiable information is collected through the use of technological tools, like:

(a) Cookies, which are small text files that are deposited on the hard drive of your computer system by default when you visit the Website to access Website service. You may refuse to accept cookies by adjusting your browser preferences. However, we strongly advise against refusing the cookies from our servers for two reasons: (i) our cookies neither compromise on your online privacy, nor do they harm your computer system in any manner whatsoever; and (b) by refusing cookies, you may not be able to access some portions of our Website service.

(b) Web Beacons, which are, essentially, clear GIF files that offer multiple benefits, like counting users who have visited Website pages or opened an e-mail and for recording the popularity of certain Website content and verifying system and server integrity.

### **Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

Your personally identifiable information so collected is used for the following purposes:

(a) to provide you with customized Website service,  
(b) to provide you with the information you specifically request from us,  
(c) to process and fulfill your requests on the Website,  
(d) to communicate with you the latest updates, news and information about the Website and Website service,  
(e) to send you notices,  
(f) to notify you about any changes made on the Website or Website service,  
(g) for any other purpose for which the use of personally identifiable information is indispensable.

You may opt-out of our mailing list in case you do not wish to receive any kind of email communications from us by clicking ‘Unsubscribe’ or sending us a request to unsubscribe at the bottom of every email you receive from us. However, we reserve the right to send important communications even if you have opted out of our mailing list.

Your personally identifiable information is strictly used in accordance with the purposes mentioned herein. We do not sell, rent or lease out or in any way, commercially exploit your personally identifiable information.

### **Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

The non-personally identifiable information so collected is used for the following purposes:

(a) to prevent repeat login during an active session, while you are browsing different pages on the Website or switching to different features of the Website services,  
(b) to improve our Website, Website content and Website service in order to deliver better and personalized services,  
(c) to study your browsing patterns for our internal research purposes,  
(d) to customize the Website service,  
(e) to speed up your searches.

Your non-personally identifiable information may be shared with our affiliates and advertising partners under strict confidentiality conditions, which prohibit such affiliates and partners from sharing such information with any other person and using such information for purposes other than those specifically agreed upon.

### **Disclosure of Information**

We do not disclose your information without your consent except as provided for herein. However, under the following circumstances, we may disclose your information without incurring any liability or without your consent:

(a) disclosure in compliance with an order from an appropriate legal entity, including court, or for the purposes of abeyance of legal processes,  
(b) disclosure to enforce our legal rights and other rights as provided for in our Terms of Use Agreement,  
(c) disclosure to prevent fraud or any other alleged illegality on the Website,  
(d) disclosure to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers or others,  
(e) disclosure to the successor-in-interest in case of sale, or substantial sale, of assets of the Company.

### **Access to Information**

You can review and update your personally identifiable information by logging into your account and managing your profile settings. Alternatively, you can send us an email at **support@hostathash.com**, with the specific request to update your personally identifiable information in our records. However, we may not be able to update all the requested information in case it violates any applicable law. Some information may be un-editable without creating a new user account.

### **Google user data**

We have sig-in with Google implemented on our website to make it easy for our clients to signup and sign-in.  
We take privacy and security seriously so when accessing Google user data, the our application only collects and stores the email address of the primary Google account which is only used to create your user account. Beyond that, we do not need any of your personal data. Although we have access to personal information that you make public, we assure that no data is collected or stored in our database. We respect our users privacy hence we do not share any of your data with third-parties. We aim to provide our customers with a reliable and secure hosting environment and we strictly follow Google’s data usage policies to protect the privacy and confidentiality of the user data we access and store.

### **Data Security**

We have implemented strong human and technological safeguards to prevent loss or misuse of your information so collected through your use of this Website or Website service. However, despite our best efforts, there cannot be a foolproof mechanism to prevent loss or unauthorized access to sensitive information stored on our servers by hackers due to rapid advancement in technology. For all such accidental or inadvertent data loss, the Company shall not be liable to anyone.

You shall be solely responsible for any authorized or unauthorized use of your account, whether the activity in your account is legitimate or otherwise. Therefore, it is important to preserve the safety and integrity of your username and password.

### **For EEA users**

HostatHash uses, stores and processes personal data, including those mentioned in the ‘Information Collection’ section. We use this data to provide you services and under contractual agreement. We rely on your consent to process Personal Data to send promotional emails and to place cookies on your devices.

We would also like to notify you that we collect, process and transfer your data to India and US, where it is stored in our local servers. By visiting or using our Services, you consent to the collection and storage of your Personal data, including the data you’ve provided as well as the data automatically collected, to servers in India and US. If you do not agree to this, please delete your account and refrain from using our services.

### **Rights of EEA Users**

Individuals located in the European Economic Area (EEA) have certain rights in respect to their personal information, including the right to access, correct, or delete Personal Data we process through your use of our website or services.

Under the EEA laws, you are applicable to:

* **Information Copy –** You can send us an email on support@hostathash.com and request a copy of the personal information that the company has on you.
* **Prevent Marketing Messages–** We only send marketing communications to users located in the EEA with your prior consent, and you can prevent us from using your information to provide you with promotional content by simply “unsubscribing” to the mailers. Please note you will continue to receive transactional messages related to our Services, even if you unsubscribe from marketing emails.
* **Updating/Deleting Information –** You can either edit and/or delete the information directly on your Dashboard or you can send us an email on support@hostathash.com to update, and/or delete information related to you. Please give us up to 5 working business days to ensure that the request is complied with.

We will consider all requests and provide our response within the time period stated by applicable law. Please note, however, that certain information may be exempt from such requests in some circumstances, which may include if we need to keep processing your information for our legitimate interests or to comply with a legal obligation. To the extent that you make such a request, we require certain information to help verify your request and prevent fraudulent information and removal requests. These including information such as username and email address associated with the account. We may also ask your billing information when it is regarding a purchasing issue. Depending on the circumstances and the information you request, we may require additional methods of verification in our discretion.

### **Contact Us**

In case you still have any questions or privacy concerns on the Website, please contact us at **support@hostathash.com** We shall strive to answer all your queries at our earliest administrative convenience.

Last Updated: 08 November 2023

#### Hosting Packages

#### Services Link

#### Quick Links

#### Payment Gateways

© Copyright 2017-2023 HostatHash | All Rights Reserved | [Terms of Service](https://hostathash.com/terms-of-service/) | [Privacy Policy](https://hostathash.com/privacy-policy/) | [Refund Policy](https://hostathash.com/refund-policy/)
